[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "How much more money do we want to steal from the American people to fund more government?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "RBR", "NN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "The Republican proposal is the worst of all worst.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Am I wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "No, you're not wrong, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "This sort of kind of goes into effect over a few days and weeks, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "And as -- and as the CEO of the country, who should call the meeting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", ":", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Right, but I think you can blame the president.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Do you see that happening here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "No, and I think it's -- it's incumbent upon the leader to make that happen, not the speaker.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "But the speaker is just as intransigent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "If I -- you have somebody -- if I were the CEO of the country, I'd be able to have a meeting when I want to have a meeting, and I'd work it out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$3.8 trillion"]}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "$", "CD", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Is it all just fiddling while Rome burns, Jack?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "We're spending $3.8 trillion while we're talking about these cuts.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"], "LOCATION": ["Rome"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Is this -- is this a problem for the Republicans that their most positive in terms of public opinion politician is already getting snubbed by the party?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "IN", "PRP$", "RBS", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "It certainly doesn't make the tent bigger, I'll tell you that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "Do you think you can get more done as a team physically together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Well, I think there's two parts to that question, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "-- but enjoyed working from home to continue?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Look, she's not going to throw out great performers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "We had it all, didn't we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "We sure did, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Ma'am, were you crying when you were shooting him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "I don't remember.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "Were you crying when you were stabbing him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "I don't remember.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Were you crying then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, has she got any chance of getting off this from everything you're hearing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "I don't think she has any chance of being acquitted.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan Dershowitz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["morning"]}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "What does she say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Well, it's 3:30 in the morning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "May I ask was that before or after she had sex with the man in Utah after she killed Travis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Utah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Did you speak to her again where she denied killing him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "That was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "That was it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "But she never gave any indication that she'd been responsible for the death?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "In what way was she addicted, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Well, and I'm not saying that, you know, he deliberately had a spell on her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Was it, from what you saw of them together -- was it an abusive relationship?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Well, I never saw them together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "From what you knew of Travis, was he an abusive character?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "No, I did not know him to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Travis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "I mean, you must have been shocked, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "I was completely shocked.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Was she somebody you wouldn't completely trust?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "No, she was completely trustworthy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "It's a classic cover your tracks, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Well, it's much worse than that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Would somebody risk their job to do that kind of research?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Well, it really is getting sinister.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Am I right to feel disquieted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Well, I think there are two things going on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "JJS", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What is your honest reaction to it all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Well, I think I may be somebody who believes in the Pope's position more than most Catholics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Don't you follow everything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "No, that's the point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Is that a good enough excuse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I don't think she needs an excuse at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Is that acceptable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "You have every right to be offended by it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "No limits?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "I think there are limits to each one of us and our tastes and what we will enjoy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Isn't that the most beautiful thing in the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Does he know what he's doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "It absolutely is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]